A Guide to the Correspondence of the Director of the Virginia Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1982-2006
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Correspondence of the Director of the Virginia Dept. of Medical Assistance Services 1982-2006
The Library of Virginia
36062, 38033, 39670, 41103, 43704, 44650
43.05 cu. ft. (45 boxes)
Virginia. Dept. of Medical Assistance Services. Director's Office.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and other protected information is considered confidential and is restricted from public access for 75 years. These files are open for access, but files may contain protected health information that must be restricted (see Code of Virginia 2.2-3705.5 and 32.1-127). It will be necessary for an archivist to review unprocessed material for confidential protected health information for removal or redaction before files can be used by patrons for research purposes or before any copies of records can be made for patrons.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1998 October 26 [Acc. 36062]; Transferred from the Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 2001 April 3 [Acc. 38033]; Transferred from the Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 2002 June 19 [Acc. 39670]; Transferred from the Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 2004 April 11 [Acc. 41103]; Transferred from the Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 2008 April 9 [Acc. 43704]; and Transferred from the Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 2009 November 23 [Acc. 44650].
Biographical Information
In 1965 President Johnson signed into law a bill creating the Medicare and Medicaid programs of the Social Security Act. The following year the General Assembly authorized the development of a medical assistance program (Medicaid) to provide comprehensive health care services to Virginia's poor. Virginia's Medicaid program became operational in 1969 under the Dept. of Health and in 1985 a separate organization entity, the Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, was created to administer the program, which was the sole function of the DMAS until 1989.
The mission of the Dept. of Medical Assistance Services is to provide information, expertise and policy recommendations that enable policy makers to plan for the provision of indigent health care services and to administer the financing of health care services to ensure access to those services for eligible persons within applicable laws and available sources. The Department strives to ensure that the categorically and medically needy citizens of the Commonwealth have financial access to cost effective, comprehensive health care delivery systems by administering the following: Medicaid program, Indigent Health Care Trust Fund, State and Local Hospital Program, Involuntary Commitment Program, Regular Assisted Living Payment for Residents of Adult Homes, Health Premium Assistance Program for HIV-positive Individuals, and the Virginia Children's Medical Security Insurance Plan Trust Fund. The Department also ensures that services are medically necessary and of acceptable quality and that services and payments are in compliance with state, federal and program regulations.
Directors include: Bruce Kozlowski (1988-1994), Robert Metcalf (1994-1996), Joseph Teefey (1997), Robert Lauterberg (1998), Dennis Smith (1998-2001), C. Mack Brankley, Acting (2001), Eric S. Bell (2001-2002), Patrick W. Finnerty (2002-). Deputy Directors include: Bruce Kozlowski (1984-1988), Patricia Watt (1989-1991), David Coronado (1991), Patricia Godbout (1991-1994), and Howard P. Estes (1998-).
Scope and Content
Correspondence and subject files, 1982-1998, of the directors and deputy directors of the Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, including correspondence, financial records, newsletters, reports, and other sundry materials. Includes correspondence from the American Public Welfare Association, Centers for Medicaid and Medicare Services, U.S. Health Care Financing Administration, and constituents, among others. Also included are Medicaid newsletters, 1994-1995. Topics include benefits and services, child care and family planning, Governor's drug control strategy, health care reform, health care costs, medical equipment and supplies, nursing homes, prescription drugs, transplantation services, among others.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Correspondence, 1984-1996 [Accession 36062]
Series II: Correspondence, 1982-1998 [Accession 38033]
Series III: Correspondence, 1993-1999 [Accession 39670]
Series IV: Correspondence, 1993-1999 [Accession 41103]
Series V: Correspondence, 1995-2002 [Accession 43704]
Series VI: Correspondence, 2001-2006 [Accession 44650].
Contents List
- Series I: Correspondence [Accession 36062], 1984-1996, Extent: 8.35 cu. ft. (9 boxes). (Box 1-9)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1991 January (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1991 February (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1991 March (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1991 April (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1991 May (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1991 June (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1991 July (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1992 January-February (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1992 February-March (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1992 March (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1992 March-April (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1992 April-May (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1992 May-June (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1992 June (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Patricia C. Watt, Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
  - Patricia C. Watt, Correspondence, 1990 January-March (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Patricia C. Watt, Correspondence, 1990 April-July (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Patricia C. Watt, Correspondence, 1990 August-December (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Patricia C. Watt, Correspondence, 1991 January-April (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Patricia C. Watt, Correspondence, 1991 April-May (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1992 June-August (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1992 August-September (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1992 September (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1992 September-October (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1992 November-December (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Patricia A. Godbout, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Patricia A. Godbout, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Patricia A. Godbout, Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Patricia A. Godbout, Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1984 December (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1985 January-February (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1985 March-May (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1985 June-August (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1985 August-September (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1986 January-April (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1986 May-June (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1986 July-August (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1986 September-October (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1986 November-1987 January (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1987 February-May (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1987 June-October (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1987 October-1988 September (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1988 October-November (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1988 November-December (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1989 January (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1989 February-March (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1989 March-April (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1989 May (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1989 June-July (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1989 July (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1989 August (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1989 September-October (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1989 November-December (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1990 January-February (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1990 February-March (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1990 March (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1990 April (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1990 May (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1990 June (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1990 July (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1990 August (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1990 September (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1990 October (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1990 November (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1990 December (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1991 January-February (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1991 February-March (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1991 March-April (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1991 April (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1991 May (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1991 May-June (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1991 June-July (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1991 July (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1991 August (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1991 August-September (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1991 September (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1991 October (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1991 November (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1991 November-December (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1992 January (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1992 February (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1992 March (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1992 March-April (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1992 May (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1992 June-July (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1992 July (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1992 August (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1992 September (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1992 October (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1992 November (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1992 December (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1993 January (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1993 February (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1993 March (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1993 April (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1993 May (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1993 June (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1993 July (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1993 August (Box 7, Folder 12-13)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1993 September (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1993 September-October (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1993 October (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1993 November (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1993 November-December (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1993 December (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1994 January (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1994 January-February (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Legislative Notebook, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
  - Misc. Administrative files, Position duties for executive secretary, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - Misc. Administrative files, Governor's Drug Control Strategy, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Administrative files, Civil action suit, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Administrative files, H.B. 1046, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Misc. Administrative files, Smart cards, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Administrative files, Child support, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Administrative files, Health care reform, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Misc. Administrative files, Contraceptive services, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Administrative files, Transplantation services, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Administrative files, DMAS positions, 1985-1990 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Misc. Administrative files, Contracting programs, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Misc. Administrative files, Correspondence, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Misc. Administrative files, Correspondence, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Misc. Administrative files, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Series II: Correspondence [Accession 38033], 1982-1985, Extent: 1.35 cu. ft. (2 boxes). (Box 1-2)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1982 March-June (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1982 July-August (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1982 September-October (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1982 November-December (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1983 January-March (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1983 April-June (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1983 July-September (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1983 October-December (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1984 January-March (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1984 April-June (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1984 July-August (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1984 September-October (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1984 October-November (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence (reply for signatures), 1982 April-December (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence (reply for signatures), 1983 January-June (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence (reply for signatures), 1983 July-September (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence (reply for signatures), 1983 October-1984 July (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence (reply for signatures), 1984 July-1985 February (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Series III: Correspondence [Accession 39670], 1982-1998, Extent: 6 cu. ft. (6 boxes). (Box 1-6)
  - Dept. of Health and Human Services, Medicaid letters (newsletter), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Public Welfare Association, Correspondence, 1998 January-May (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - USI/NHCA (National Health Care Affiliates, Inc.), Volume I, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - USI/NHCA (National Health Care Affiliates, Inc.), Volume II, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
  - Documentation of Audit Delay by Provider, USI/NHCA Form application, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - NHPS (Nursing Home Payment System), Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - NHPS, Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - NHPS, Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - NHPS, Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - NHPS, Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 5-8)
  - Robert C. Metcalf, Correspondence, 1996 January-March (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
  - Howard P. Estes, Correspondence, 1998 May-July (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Howard P. Estes, Correspondence, 1998 July-August (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Howard P. Estes, Correspondence, 1998 September (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Howard P. Estes, Correspondence, 1998 September-October (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Howard P. Estes, Correspondence, 1998 October-December (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bruce U. Kozlowski, Correspondence, 1994 February-May (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Robert C. Metcalf, Correspondence, 1994 June-September (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Robert C. Metcalf, Correspondence, 1994 October-December (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Robert C. Metcalf, Correspondence, 1995 January-February (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Robert C. Metcalf, Correspondence, 1995 March (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Robert C. Metcalf, Correspondence, 1995 April-May (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Robert C. Metcalf, Correspondence, 1995 June (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Robert C. Metcalf, Correspondence, 1995 July-August (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Robert C. Metcalf, Correspondence, 1995 September-October (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Robert C. Metcalf, Correspondence, 1995 November-December (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1989-1994 December (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1995 January-December (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1996 January-March (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1996 April-May (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1996 June-July (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1996 August-September (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1996 October (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1996 November-December (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Series IV: Correspondence [Accession 41103], 1993-1999, Extent: 6 cu. ft. (6 boxes). (Box 1-6)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1993 January-March (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1993 February-March (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1993 April-May (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1993 May-July (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1993 July-September (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1993 September (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1993 September-October (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1993 November (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1993 November-1994 January (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1994 January-February (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1994 February-March (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1994 March-April (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1994 April-June (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1994 June-August (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1994 August (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1994 September-October (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1994 October (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1994 October-December (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, Correspondence, 1994 December (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Medicaid Letters [No. 94-01 - 94-16], 1994 January-March (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Medicaid Letters [No. 94-17 - 94-38], 1994 March (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Medicaid Letters [No. 94-39 - 94-59], 1994 April-May (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Medicaid Letters [No. 94-60 - 94-89], 1994 June-August (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Medicaid Letters [No. 94-90 - 94-126], 1994 August-December (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 January 1-8 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 January 8-20 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 January 20-31 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 February 1-13 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 February 13-21 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 February 21-28 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 March 1-14 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 March 17-24 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 March 24-31 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 April 1-15 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 April 15-22 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 April 22-30 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 May 1-14 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 May 14-30 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 June 1-10 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 June 11-25 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 June 25-30 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 July (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 August (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 September (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 October (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 November (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Joseph M. Teefy, Correspondence, 1997 December (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Robert W. Lauterberg, Correspondence, 1998 January (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Robert W. Lauterberg, Correspondence, 1998 February (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Robert W. Lauterberg, Correspondence, 1998 March (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Robert W. Lauterberg, Correspondence, 1998 April (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Robert W. Lauterberg, Correspondence, 1998 May (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Robert W. Lauterberg, Correspondence, 1998 June (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Robert W. Lauterberg, Correspondence, 1998 July (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1998 August (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1998 September 1-17 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1998 September 17-30 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1998 October (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1998 November (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1998 December (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1998, Misc. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 January-February (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 March (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 April 1-16 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 April 19-30 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 May (Box 5, Folder 3-7)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 June 1-11 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 June 12-21 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 June 22-30 (Box 5, Folder 10)